nhanow.com 2017-09-10

# Privacy Policy | National Healthcareer Association

**Privacy Policy**  
Welcome to nhanow.com. This website is owned and operated by Assessment Technologies Institute, LLC, 11161 Overbrook Road, Leawood, Kansas 66211, USA (ATI), doing business as National Healthcareer Association (together with ATI, “NHA,” “we,” “us,” or “our”).  This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains to visitors (“you”) how we collect, use and disclose personal information that we obtain through this website.

CERTAIN NHA WEBSITES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PASSWORD PROTECTED SITES, CONTAIN TERMS OF USE WHICH CONTAIN PRIVACY STATEMENTS THAT ARE SPECIFIC TO THE PURPOSES OF THOSE WEBSITES.  SUCH PRIVACY STATEMENTS MAY BE IN ADDITION TO OR DIFFERENT FROM THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND THE PRIVACY STATEMENTS MADE ON SUCH WEBSITES SHALL APPLY.

**Data Collection**  
NHA is dedicated to protecting the privacy of all personal information collected through this website. We may collect personal information during the login process used to access certain portions of our website or to use other functions or features, as noted. NHA may collect and use personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, the following: name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, employer, title, user ID and password, IP address. Any demographic information we request is generally used in aggregate form for various analyses conducted by NHA regarding our website and related materials.

**Use of Information Collected on NHA’s Site**  
We use personal information to provide the highest quality of service to our customers, prospects, and general visitors to this website. NHA may collect personal information in connection with any online employment applications, or so that we can contact you, provide materials to you upon your request, register you, send relevant messages via e-mail or postal mail, or for any other purpose identified when personal information is collected. NHA may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current products and services or of potential new services that may be offered.

**Information Sharing**  
NHA will not sell, rent, trade or lease your personal information to others unless we have requested to do so and have received your permission, provided that you authorize NHA to disclose your personal information to others under the following circumstances: We may, and you authorize NHA to, transfer your personal information to any NHA affiliate (or business partner or agent acting on our behalf) worldwide for purposes described herein. Such NHA affiliates, business partners, and agents will be under the same obligations as is NHA under this Privacy Policy.  We may be required to transfer your personal information by law or under a court order or in connection with an organizational change, such as a merger or acquisition by another company or the sale of NHA’s assets. If NHA, in its sole discretion, determines that a transfer is necessary to protect the rights, property, or security of NHA, this site or its users or the personal safety of individuals, then we also may share your personal information.

**Data Protection**  
NHA is committed to ensuring the security of your information. We use industry-standard processes designed to protect sensitive data, however, because of the nature of the internet, we cannot guarantee the security of the information you transmit, so you should take precautions to protect your personal information when you are on the internet, such as changing passwords often, using a combination of letters and numbers when creating passwords, and using a secure browser.

**Consent**  
By use of the NHA website, and entry of any personal information into this site, you are consenting to the collection, use, and transfer of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy.  If you are located outside the United States, your use and entry of personal information into this site constitutes your consent to the transfer of your personal information into the United States. Although we do not normally collect any sensitive personal information (such as ethnicity or race, religious beliefs or medical conditions), your entry of any such sensitive information on this website is your express consent to the collection, use and transfer of such information.

**Cookies and other Tracking Devices**  
NHA may use cookies, IP addresses, and other passive tracking devices to collect aggregate statistics about our website. We use this information to monitor the performance of this site so we can improve its use and add features and programs to make it more effective. NHA also may aggregate and disclose this information to third parties. You may choose to set your browser settings to disable cookies, however, please note that if you do so, you may not be able to complete certain activities or access certain information on our website. 

**Links**  
NHA’s website may contain links to other websites, including those of NHA’s affiliated companies. Please note that these other websites’ privacy policies may differ from NHA’s and we encourage you to carefully read those policies, as well. NHA is not responsible for the contents of any website of another party.

**Revisions to this Privacy Policy**  
NHA reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time, without notice, so please review this Privacy Policy frequently. Each version of this Privacy Policy will have a date, noted below.

**Feedback**  
If you have any questions or comments about NHA’s Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at  [info@nhanow.com](mailto:info@nhanow.com)

  NHA Privacy Policy (Rev Sept2016)
